Urika Pye

Signal Support Systems Specialist - US ARMY NATIONAL GUARD

Jacksonville, FL Urika.Pye@gmail.com (404)-416-3258

To be able to work and do my best job, one that is suited to my skills, talent and experience, and to be of service in my full ability for the benefit of my employer.

VALUE OFFER

A highly accomplished and driven customer service professional with broad-based expertise in technical support, billing, filing, and report preparation. Takes on additional responsibilities to ensure the achievement of organizational goals. Works well during high-pressure situations and consistently delivers top results. Serves as a hardworking team member and/or works independently with a high sense of urgency and a solid commitment to excellence. Poised and competent with demonstrated ability to easily transcend cultural differences. Possesses the ability to rapidly learn new information and adapt to challenging environments.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Work Experience

Supervisor

Staffing Solutions - Remote September 2020 to Present

Responsible for the development of the lower-level agents and their growth with the project. Learned to deal with and address different personality types and build trust, respect, and accountability with each personality type. Also learned to multi-task in a higher paced environment and meet deadlines for each assignment.

- Assist cardholders with unemployment and/or child support accounts with their banking information and how to find out more information about their deposits.
- Assisted cardholders with disputes, status of their disputes, resetting their card when it locks, and verifying flagged transactions.
- Assist agents with increasing their quality scores, reaching their goals with the company, and showing where to find the answer to their questions. I also take escalated calls from cardholders, when the previous representatives are unable to de-escalate them.
- Mastered my customer service skillset to become better at de-escalating clients, resolving any issues that may arise, and building rapport for consistent business.

Signal Support Systems Specialist

US ARMY NATIONAL GUARD - Montgomery, AL August 2016 to Present

Responsible for working with battlefield signal support systems and terminal devices needed to direct the movement of its troops. Learned mechanical and electrical principles, preventive maintenance procedures, line installation and wiring techniques and strong problem-solving skills.

- Maintain radio and data distribution systems.
- Perform signal support functions and technical assistance for computer systems.
- Provide technical assistance and training for local-area networks.
- Maintain equipment, terminal devices, assigned vehicles and power generators.

Call Center Representative

TRC Staffing - Montgomery, AL August 2018 to January 2019

Promoted our programs and how they worked, explained billing cycles, worked with customers concerning the status of their accounts and coming up with the best solution for them and the company by setting up payment arrangements all while maintaining the highest level of professionalism and customer service.

- Received inbound phone calls from clients and assisted them using multiple resources.
- Responded to client inquiries and performed follow-ups with clients.
- Maintained file notes of communications with clients.
- Ensured a positive customer service experience for all clients.

Technical Support Agent, USA

Sykes, inc

July 2015 to September 2016

Listened to customers' wants, needs and interests before connecting them to our products and solutions. Developed strong problem-solving skills with a passion to help those in need and see things through with an increased desire to learn more.

- Assisted customers with questions and problems; researched and provided resolutions.
- Provided technical support to troubleshoot issues.
- Solved problems by use of conceptual thinking.
- Prepared complete and accurate work including appropriately notating accounts as required.

Education

Coding Bootcamp in Full Stack Web Development

University of Central Florida

December 2020 to Present

High school diploma in BAS

AUBURN UNIVERSITY AT MONTGOMERY - Montgomery, AL

August 2012 to May 2016

Skills

• HTML (Less than 1 year)

- CSS (Less than 1 year)
- Git (Less than 1 year)
- GitHub (Less than 1 year)
- JavaScript (Less than 1 year)
- Web APIs (Less than 1 year)
- Third-Party APIs (Less than 1 year)
- Server-Side APIs (Less than 1 year)
- Bootstrap (Less than 1 year)
- JQuery (Less than 1 year)
- Virtual Private Network (4 years)
- Virtual Studio Code (Less than 1 year)
- VS Code (Less than 1 year)
- MySQL (Less than 1 year)
- Node.js (Less than 1 year)
- OOP (Less than 1 year)
- Express.js (Less than 1 year)
- SQL (Less than 1 year)
- SQLite (Less than 1 year)
- MVC (Less than 1 year)
- NoSQL (Less than 1 year)
- React (Less than 1 year)
- GraphQL (Less than 1 year)
- MongoDB (Less than 1 year)
- Java (Less than 1 year)
- AJAX (Less than 1 year)
- JSON (Less than 1 year)
- Heroku (Less than 1 year)
- Python (Less than 1 year)
- AWS (Less than 1 year)
- REST (Less than 1 year)
- Relational databases (Less than 1 year)
- Front-end development (Less than 1 year)
- Back-end development (Less than 1 year)
- APIs (Less than 1 year)
- User Interface (UI) (Less than 1 year)
- Web Services (Less than 1 year)
- Software development (Less than 1 year)
- 10 key calculator (9 years)
- Handlebars (Less than 1 year)
- Web development (Less than 1 year)

https://www.github.com/UPye

Military Service

Branch: United States Army National Guard

Service Country: United States

Rank: PFC

August 2016 to Present

Assessments

Memorization — Expert

November 2019

Committing product or merchandise information to memory and recalling it at a later time.

Full results: Expert

Data entry: Attention to detail — Expert

January 2020

Maintaining data integrity by detecting errors

Full results: Expert

Project timeline management — Highly Proficient

January 2020

Prioritizing and allocating time to effectively achieve project deliverables

Full results: Highly Proficient

Data entry: Accuracy — Highly Proficient

October 2020

Entering data quickly and accurately

Full results: Highly Proficient

Attention to detail — Expert

November 2019

Identifying differences in materials, following instructions, and detecting details among distracting

information.

Full results: Expert

Real estate — Expert

January 2020

Matching listings with specifications

Full results: Expert

Software developer fit — Highly Proficient

April 2021

Measures the traits that are important for successful software developers

Full results: <u>Highly Proficient</u>

Logic & critical thinking — Highly Proficient

October 2020

Using logic to solve problems. Full results: <u>Highly Proficient</u>

Indeed Assessments provides skills tests that are not indicative of a license or certification, or continued development in any professional field.

Additional Information

COMPUTER SKILLS

Microsoft Office Word, Excel, Outlook, PowerPoint, Access, Works, Adobe; Windows, Desktop Support, Apple